Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - Maiesha performing with Maiesha and the Hip Huggers at Go-Go Under the Stars at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery, 2011-07-31; 199chippy_0665; Maiesha performing with microphone at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery.
  - Sweet Cherie performing at Go-Go Under the Stars at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery, 2011-07-31; 199chippy_0666; Sweet Cherie performing with microphone with band members at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery.
  - Blue-Eye performing at Go-Go Under the Stars at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery, 2011-07-31; 199chippy_0667; Blue-Eye wearing headphones and playing drums at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery.
  - Blue-Eye performing at Go-Go Under the Stars at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery, 2011-07-31; 199chippy_0668; Blue-Eye wearing headphones and playing drums at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery.
  - D. Floyd and RB performing at Go-Go Under the Stars at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery, 2011-07-31; 199chippy_0669; From left to right D. Floyd holds a microphone in his left hand and sings and RB looks on while performing with at Go-Go Under the Stars.
  - D. Floyd and Maiesha performing at Go-Go Under the Stars at Anacostia Boutique and Gallery, 2011-07-31; 199chippy_0670; D. Floyd holds a microphone with his left hand while performing with at Go-Go Under the Stars. To the right Maiesha is visible.
  - Halima Peru and Doc performing with the Faycez U Know Band at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0584; Halima Peru sings into a microphone with a scarf tied around on it on stage Faycez U Know Band at Marygolds Family Event Center. Doc can be seen playing guitar in the background.
  - Kal-El Gross performs with Faycez U Know Band at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0585; Kal-El Gross sings on stage with the Faycez U Know Band at Marygolds Family Event Center. Another band member can be seen playing the tambourine.
  - Fan dances on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0586; Fan dances on stage at Marygolds Family Event Center. This fan's name is likely Becky. Other fans can be seen.
  - Kool Kirky on percussion with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0587; Kool Kirky plays the cowbell with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center. A set of drums sits below Kirky.
  - Stomp Dogg performing with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0588; Stomp Dogg smiles while playing drums with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - DJ Frisco dances with a fan at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0589; DJ Frisco (left) dances with a fan at Marygolds Family Event Center. The fan is likely known as Becky.
  - 32 and Showtyme perform with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0590; 32 (right) and Showtyme (left) sing on stage with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - 32 performing with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0591; 32 sings into a microphone while performing with Da Mixx. Other band members are visible.
  - 32 performing with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0592; 32 sings into a microphone while performing with Da Mixx. Other band members are visible.
  - Horn section of Da Mixx performs at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0593; Horn section of Da Mixx performs at Marygolds Family Event Center.
  - Fans at Da Mixx show at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0594; Fans pose at a Da Mixx performance at Marygold Family Event Center.
  - GoGo Smoke plays congas with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0595; GoGo Smoke performs on congas with Da Mixx at Marygold Family Event Center.
  - Trombone player performs with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0596; Trombone player performs with Da Mixx at Marygold Family Event Center.
  - Stomp Dogg performs with Da Mixx at Marygolds Family Event Center, 2011-08-04; 199chippy_0597; Stomp Dogg performs on drums with Da Mixx at Marygold Family Event Center.
  - Kacey Williams performing with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0493; Kacey Williams stretches out her arms as she performs with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club. A performer playing the keyboard is in the background.
  - Kacey Williams performing with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0494; Kacey Williams holds a microphone as she performs with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club.
  - Animal performing with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0495; Animal performs with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club.
  - Animal performing with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0496; Animal performs with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club.
  - Kacey Williams performing with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0497; Kacey Williams gestures with her left arm as she performs with BLACK ALLEY at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club.
  - BLACK ALLEY drummers at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0498; Animal and another drummer perform on stage with congas, drum kits, congas and plastic pails.
  - BLACK ALLEY drummers at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0499; Animal and another drummer perform on stage with congas, drum kits, congas and plastic pails.
  - Backstage at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0500; Rock Newman sitting with band members in a room eating and drinking.
  - Christopher Lee and Brad Clements backstage at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0501; Brand Clements playing trumpet to Christopher Lee in stairwell.
  - Kwick Foot and Animal backstage at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0502; Kwick Foot and Animal standing together in front of equipment cases.
  - DJ Dirty Rico on stage with Chuck Brown at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0503; DJ Dirty Rico and Chuck Brown on stage in front of the audience while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Chuck Brown playing electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band at his 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0504; Chuck Brown on stage playing an electric guitar with Chuck Brown Band in front of a standing room only audience.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at his 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0505; Chuck Brown standing in front of microphone playing an electric guitar with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0506; Kwick Foot seated playing drum kit while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at his 75th Birthday Bash at the 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0507; Cuck Brown with a microphone and electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band. In the audience are fans with outstretched hands.
  - Ice, Greg Boyer, Brad Clements, and Bryan Mills performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0508; Ice plays bass guitar with his back to the audience. Behind him left to right are Greg Boyer on trombone, Brad Clements, and Bryan Mills. The musicians are performing with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0509; Kwick Foot plays drums with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. Sweet Cherie is visible to the right.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0510; Sweet Cherie sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. She holds the microphone in her right hand and looks into the audience.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0511; Sweet Cherie sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. She holds the microphone in her right hand.
  - D. Floyd and Ice performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0512; Ice lays down the bottom beat on the bass guitar while D. Floyd sings to the crowd. Greg Boyer is visible to the right.
  - Chuck Brown holding notes for 'shout outs' at his 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0513; Chuck Brown holds notes in his hands for 'call outs' during his 75th Birthday Bash with Chuck Brown Band. He is wearing a guitar across his chest. Members of the audience look at something out of frame.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0514; Kwick Foot plays drums with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0515; Greg Boyer points at the audience while performing with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. He holds a trombone in his left hand. Brand Clements holding a trumpet is visible to the right.
  - D. Floyd 'checks the clock' with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0516; D. Floyd 'checks the clock' while performing with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. He holds a microphone in his right hand. In front of him the audience is pressed against the stage and many are dancing.
  - D. Floyd and Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0517; From left to right D. Floyd sings and holds a microphone while Greg Boyer holds a trombone and dances while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. In the background the audience is pressed against the stage and dances.
  - Raheem DeVaughn performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0518; Raheem DeVaughn interacts with the audience while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. A fan has wrapped their hands around DeVaughn's wrist.
  - Big G points a microphone while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0519; Big G points a microphone at the audience while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Big G listens to fans while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0520; Big G cups his left ear to listen to the audience while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash.
  - KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0521; KK holds a microphone in her right hand and sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Ledisi and Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0522; Ledisi holds a microphone in her right hand and sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. Chuck Brown is visible in the background to the right.
  - D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0523; D. Floyd signs while performing with Chuck Brown Band during Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. He holds a microphone in his right hand. Jas. Funk is visible in the background.
  - Jas. Funk performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0524; Jas. Funk sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash. He holds a microphone in his right hand.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at his 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0525; Chuck Brown smiling while performing with Chuck Brown Band at his 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at his 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0526; Chuck Brown smiling while performing with Chuck Brown Band at his 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Chuck Brown at his 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0527; Chuck Brown smokes a cigar at his 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Kevin Jones and Chuck Brown at his 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0528; From left to right Chuck Brown poses with long-time fan Kevin Jones at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash.
  - DJ Blakberri and Chuck Brown's at his 75th Birthday Bash at 9:30 Club, 2011-08-11; 199chippy_0529; From left to right Chuck Brown poses with DJ Blakberri at Chuck Brown's 75th Birthday Bash.
  - Chuck Brown smokes a cigar in his Mercedes, 2011-08-20; 199chippy_0488; Chuck Brown sits in his new Mercedes. A Black and Mild cigar is in his mouth.
  - Chuck Brown performing 'The Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation, 2011-08-20; 199chippy_0489; Chuck Brown performs 'The Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation. A canned beverage is in his left hand.
  - Chuck Brown performing 'The Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation, 2011-08-20; 199chippy_0490; Chuck Brown performs 'The Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation. A canned beverage is in his left hand.
  - Chuck Brown performing 'The Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation, 2011-08-20; 199chippy_0491; Chuck Brown performs 'The Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation. A canned beverage is in his left hand. A performer playing the keyboard is in the background.
  - Chuck Brown performing 'The Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation, 2011-08-20; 199chippy_0492; Chuck Brown performs 'the Numbers Game' with Thievery Corporation. A canned beverage is in his left hand. A performer playing the keyboard is in the background.
  - Thomas Sayers Ellis takes photos during a BE'LA DONA performance at WOW Café and Wingery, 2011-08-22; 199chippy_0293; Thomas Sayers Ellis takes photos during a BE'LA DONA performance at WOW Café and Wingery.
  - Fan at a BE'LA DONA show at WOW Café and Wingery, 2011-08-22; 199chippy_0294; Fan shows off a t-shirt that reads 'Be'la Dona' during a BE'LA DONA performance at WOW Café and Wingery.
  - Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA during a performance at WOW Café and Wingery, 2011-08-22; 199chippy_0295; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA during a performance at WOW Café and Wingery.
  - L Boogie performs with BE'LA DONA during a performance at WOW Café and Wingery, 2011-08-22; 199chippy_0296; L Boogie performs as percussionist with BE'LA DONA during a performance at WOW Café and Wingery.
  - Fan plays cowbell at a BE'LA DONA show at WOW Cafe and Wingery, 2011-08-22; 199chippy_0297; Fan plays a cowbell during a BE'LA DONA performance at WOW Café and Wingery.
  - Sugar Rai performs with BE'LA DONA during a performance at WOW Café and Wingery, 2011-08-22; 199chippy_0298; Sugar Rai performs with tambourine during a BE'LA DONA performance at WOW Café and Wingery.
  - Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at WOW Café and Wingery, 2011-08-22; 199chippy_0299; Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA during a performance at WOW Café and Wingery.
  - Vocalist performs with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill, 2011-08-24; 199chippy_0612; Vocalist performs with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill.
  - Vocalist performs with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill, 2011-08-24; 199chippy_0613; Vocalist performs with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill.
  - Vocalists perform with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill, 2011-08-24; 199chippy_0614; Vocalists perform with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill.
  - Vocalists perform with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill, 2011-08-24; 199chippy_0615; Vocalists perform with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill.
  - Vocalists perform with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill, 2011-08-24; 199chippy_0616; Vocalists perform with Dynasty Band at My Place Sports Bar and Grill.
  - KK performing with Chuck Brown Band on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0456; KK smiles before a performance with Chuck Brown Band on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown, KK, and Cookie at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0457; Chuck Brown opens birthday gifts in his trailer from his daughters KK (left) and Cookie (right) at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown and KK in his trailer at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0458; Chuck Brown smiles as he sits with his daughter KK in his trailer before performing at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown with a lemon at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0459; Chuck Brown holds a lemon before performing at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0460; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra the National Symphony Orchestra on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0461; Chuck Brown sings into a microphone while performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall. Several National Symphony Orchestra members are visible in the background.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0462; Chuck Brown sings into a microphone performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0463; Chuck Brown sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0464; Chuck Brown sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0465; Chuck Brown sings while performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0466; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0467; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0468; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0469; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0470; Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra perform at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall. Seven performers are in the background. Sweet Cherie is at the keyboard. Chuck Brown plays electric guitar and Sweet Cherie plays the keys. Other musicians are visible in the background..
  - Chuck Brown Band performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0471; Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra perform at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall. Seven performers are in the background. Sweet Cherie is at the keyboard. Chuck Brown plays electric guitar and Sweet Cherie plays the keys. Other musicians are visible in the background..
  - Chuck Brown Band performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0472; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall. In the background Sweet Cherie on keys and other musicians are visible..
  - Brad Clements performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0473; Brad Clements plays the trumpet as he performs with Chuck Brown at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown and Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0474; Chuck Brown plays the electric guitar as he performs at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall. Sweet Cherie plays the keyboard behind him.
  - Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0475; Greg Boyer plays the trombone as he performs with Chuck Brown Band at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Chuck Brown performing on the West Lawn of the United States Capitol at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0476; Chuck Brown plays the guitar as he performs at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall. Sweet Cherie is behind him.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0477; Kwick Foot plays the drums as he performs with Chuck Brown Band at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall.
  - Mr. Marcus Young performing with Chuck Brown Band and the National Symphony Orchestra at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall, 2011-09-04; 199chippy_0478; Mr. Marcus Young plays the keyboard as he performs with Chuck Brown at the Labor Day Concert on the National Mall. Ice Can be seen in the background.